Sutton Sabinash

I provide accounting services that empower business growth!

Milwaukee, WI 53224

suttonsabinash5_ohe@indeedemail.com

"I understand that handling, making sense of, and utilizing numbers to thrive is a daunting challenge. It's what fuels my passion for accounting and finance. It's allowed me to utilize my skillset to empower business owners and their businesses alike. Holding titles of VP of Finance and CFO at companies from the startup phase to \$45 million/year in revenue, I have had the pleasure of transforming companies' trajectories by using their financials as a road map to where they want to go. This attitude and these practices are what motivated me and set the foundation to creating Every Second Accounts, an accounting experience unlike any other."

#readytowork

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Founder

Every Second Accounts - Milwaukee, WI November 2017 to Present

- Bookkeeping
- o Daily Transaction Posting
- o Monthly Financial Reporting
- · Accounts Payable
- o Verifying, processing, and reconciling vendor invoices
- o Handling payment cycle in a timely and efficient manner
- Accounts Receivable
- o Maintaining customer billing
- o Verifying and posting payment receipts
- o Invoice collections
- Full Financials
- o Handling, directing, and coordinating all accounting functions o Advise owner(s) with information vital to decision making
- CFO

Various - Milwaukee, WI September 2013 to November 2017 Previous Titles Held:

VP of Finance / CFO / Controller / Senior Accountant

Industries Include (but not limited to):

Manufacturing / E-Commerce / Agencies / Non-Profit / Real Estate / Law / Retail

Education

Bachelor's in Accounting

Lakeland University - Milwaukee, WI June 2014 to August 2018

Skills

- · Financial Report Writing
- Accounts Receivable
- General Ledger Accounting
- Accounting
- Payroll
- Bank Reconciliation
- Bookkeeping
- · Accounts Payable
- Account Reconciliation
- Journal Entries
- Balance Sheet Reconciliation
- QuickBooks
- Auditing
- Office Management
- E-Commerce
- Forecasting
- Financial Statement Preparation
- Business Analysis
- Forecasting
- Business Analysis
- Financial Analysis
- GAAP
- Financial Statement Preparation
- E-Commerce
- Tax Experience

Links

http://everysecondaccounts.com

http://linkedin.com/in/suttonsabinash